

VITALII BULATNIKOV PYTHON DEVELOPER

DATE OF BIRTH: 05.10.1996

I have a work permit. Ready to move immediately to any region of Europe. In addition, I'm ready to work remotely with pleasure

(+39-328-218-23-02

bvr-job@hotmail.com

🗣 Italy, Emiglia Romagna, Rimini

www.taplink.cc/b9v6r



LANGUAGES

Russian

English

Italian

EDUCATION

Specialist in transport and transport management,

International Novorossiysk Maritime University named **Admiral F. F. Ushakov**, 2016-2021

Computer security technician for automated systems,

Novorossivsk Radio Instrumentation College, 2012-2016

COURSES

Administration MySQL, Sovcombank Technologies, 2022

Programming in Python, Stepik, 2021

Administrating Linux & Windows servers, Cisco, 2022

> Front-end development, ITVDN, **2023**

HARD SKILLS

Widows

Administration

Python

Programming

MySQL

Active Directory

Linux(Debian)

Administration

ERP

SOFT SKILLS

Use Al assistants

Team player

Fast Learner

Multifunctional

Proactive



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a beginner Python developer, focused on finding employment and ready for learning and growth. I have experience working with various libraries and frameworks, including Cryptography, OpenPyXL, Kivy, PyQt, Flask, Tkinter, Pygame, and MySQL.

My skills also extend to the field of Windows administration, Linux, and networking technologies. I have experience working as a system administrator.

I am passionately interested in software development and strive for continuous learning and self-improvement. I quickly learn new technologies and am ready to take on challenges that may arise during project work.

My goal is to create high-quality software solutions and actively participate in projects that contribute to my professional and personal growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREE SPECIALIST

2023 - NOW

- ITALY, RIMINI
- Freelance work

· Work in other profession

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

2022 - 2022

MULTIFUNCTIONAL SURGICAL CLINIC, RUSSIA, NOVOROSSIYSK

- Support web site company (html, WordPress)
- Maintenance, repair, debugging of computer systems and communications equipment (Linux Server, Erp, Windows)
- Write various system utilities in python and cmd for Windows computers in order to optimize user workflows
- · Write various utilities in bash for necessary functioning of the server

IT SYSTEMS SPECIALIST

2021-2022

SOVCOMBANK TECHNOLOGIES, RUSSIA, NOVOROSSIYSK

- \bullet Maintenance, repair, debugging of computer systems and communication hardware (Hardware / Software level)
- Maintaining inventory records of computer systems
- Information security incident response
- Provide technical support for computer equipment to bank employees